

# Sulabh Majumder

## Salesforce Developer

## **My Contact**

sulabh21198@gmail.com

( 9679186353

Kolkata, India

www.linkedin.com/in/sulabhmajumder-1b68b1186

#### **Hard Skill**

- Salesforce Development
- Apex, Batch classes, Triggers, Test Classes
- Lighting Web Component (LWC)
- Report, Dashboard
- Flow, Process Builder, Workflow Rule
- Documentation
- Visualforce

#### **Soft Skill**

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- Team work

## **Education Background**

#### JIS College of Engineering

B.Tech, Computer science & Engineering 7.65 Completed in 2020

Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya

Higher secondary, Science Completed in 2016

Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya

Matriculation
Completed in 2014

#### **About Me**

Salesforce developer with 2 years of experience in Salesforce development, Apex, Lighting, Testing, flow and LWC. Is skilled at deploying agile practices to optimize processes. Worked in project and participated in making various proof of concept and bringing them to life and implementing them. I am Upbeat self independent team player with good communication and analytical skills, strategic planning and interpersonal. Highly motivated, enthusiastic and self-starter.

## **Professional Experience**

Capgemini, Senior software developer 2021 – Present
Project Description: Agent Dashboard (2021 - Present), Making
various component for dashboard with Salesforce tools, creating
flexpage with LWC to visualize data coming from Salesforce object.
Creating batch classes and triggers for updating records and
sending notification to user on certain events. Sending email to
admin if any error occurs in any of the components in production.

#### **Key responsibilities:**

- Analyze the stories in **JIRA**, and provide estimation for it.
- Making Design Documentation for the story or task.
- Working on developing the stories using Apex, LWC, flow or other salesforce tools using IDE like VS code.
- Unit testing all the components with different possibilities.
- Using tools like **Bitbucket**, **Ant** for code migration and code hosting.
- Making any post deployment documents if necessary.
   Delivering the items.

## <u>Personal Project</u>

WINE QUALITY TESTING USING MACHINE LEARNING 12/2018 - 01/2019

This is a supervised learning based model to predict the quality of a wine. (red wine and white wine)

## **Achievements**

2015 Got into and played kho-kho, in

regional level.

2021-2022 Successfully deploying multiple time in

production release for general public

use, for the client.

2023 Microsoft Certified: Azure

fundamental certification (AZ-900).